So, here I am, back at the code, and
那么 我在这儿 回到代码中 然后
here I can see my class movie, and within it
这里我看见我的类 movie 然后在里面
I will begin to define, [SOUND] the function, init.
我会开始定义 这个函数 init
Now, there is something very curious about this function already,
现在 这个函数有一个特别令人好奇的地方
which is that, there are two underscores on both
就是 在单词 init 的两边都有
sides of the word in it. These underscores are a
双下划线 这些下划线是 Python
way for Python to tell us, the programmers, that hey,
的一种方式告诉我们 程序员 嘿
the name init, is essentially reserved in Python, and that,
这个名字 init 是在 Python 的基本中保留的 于是
this is a special function or method. What's
这是一个特殊的函数或者方法 init
special about init? Is that, it initializes or creates
有什么特殊的呢？ 是这样 它初始化或者在内存中
space in memory. To remember details like title, story
创建空间 来记住像标题 故事情节 之类
line, et cetera, for new movies that we are
这样的细节 对于我们将要创建的
about to create. Now init, takes a few
新的电影实例 现在 init 接收一些
pieces of information or arguments. The first of which,
信息或者参数 其第一个
is always the python keyword, self. Now, what is
总会是 python 关键字 self 现在
this thing called, self, you ask? Well, you can
这个调用的 self 是什么呢？ 好吧 你可以
think of self as itself, or the instance being created.
把 self 认为是它自己 或者被创建的实例自己
So, when we run this line of code in our
所以 当我们在其他 Python 文件运行
other Python file, by the way, just to remind you,
这行代码 顺便一提 只是为了提醒你
here we are trying to create a new movie called, toy_story.
这里我们想要创建一个新的电影叫 toy_story
And when we run this line of code, we know
然后当我们运行这行代码时 我们知道
that the __init__ function inside the class Movie gets called. Self,
在类 Movie 中函数 __init__ 被调用 Self
in that case, points to toy_story. Now here, I have
在这个例子中 指向 toy_story 现在 我需要
a confession to make. I remember when I was first learning
坦白一件事 我记得多年前在大学时当我
object oriented programming years ago in college. This concept of
第一次学到面向对象编程 这个 self 的概念
self, was really difficult for me to understand. If that
对我来说十分的难理解 如果
is the case with you, don't worry about it too
你也是这样 现在别太
much for now. This will get, really clear when we
担心 它会在我们学习这个整个
learn this entire piece of coding a few seconds. In
代码一会儿后变得清晰起来
any case, let's add the keyword self, to our list
总之 让我们加上这个关键字 self 到我们的
of new words. Okay, I'm going to go back to
新词列表中 好的 我将回到
the class movie, and continue to define the function, init.
类 movie 并接着定义函数 init
Now, we want init, to initialize pieces of information like title, story line
现在 我们想 init 来初始化如标题 故事情节之类的信息和
and others that we want to remember inside our class. Here's a way to do that. I
其他我们想要在类中记得的 一种做到的方法是 我
will say, self.title, then self.storyline.
会调用 self.title 接着 self.storyline
[SOUND] The next one is, poster_image_url, and
下一个是 poster_image_url
finally, trailer_youtube_url. Now, we have to somehow initialize
最终 trailer_youtube_url 现在 我们必须初始化
these variables, with information init is going to
这些变量 与 init 收入的信息
receive. And in particular, it's going to receive, four
一起 接着尤其是 它将接收 四个
pieces of information. The first of which is,
信息 第一个是
a movie title, [SOUND] next is, the movie storyline,
电影标题 下一个是 电影故事情节
then the poster image of the movie, and
接着电影的海报
finally, the trailer on YouTube. So,get this, once I've
最后 在 Youtube 上的预告 所以 看这个 一旦我
received these four pieces of information as arguments to
接收到这四个信息并作为参数给
the __init__ function, I can initialize my Movie variables.
__init__ 函数 我可以初始化我的 Movie 变量
Here's how to do that. self.title, is the movie
这里是怎么做 self.title 是电影
title. Self.storyline, is the movie story line. Next is,
标题 Self.storyline 是电影故事情节 下一个是
[SOUND] the poster image. And finally, [SOUND] the trailer
海报图 接着最后 在
on youtube. Now here, I have a confession to
youtube 上的预告 现在 我坦白
make. Which is, that we've written a lot of
一下 就是 我们已经写了很多
code that looks new and strange. Well, the one
看上去新且奇怪的代码 好吧 我要说
thing I can say is that, we should all
的一件事是 我们应该
just take a pause and a deep breath together.
都休息一下并深呼吸
[SOUND]. For now, all I want you to do, is
现在 我想让你做的是
pause this video, and write down this code on your
暂停这个视频 接着在你的电脑上写下
computer. All of this code will make sense as soon
这个代码 一旦我们运行这个程序这个代码
as we run this program. Now, there is one key point
的一切会变得有道理起来 现在 有一个关键点
I would like to highlight, before I execute this piece
我想标起来 在我执行这个
of code, which is, that if I go to my
代码前 就是 如果我打开
other Python file, which is entertainment_center.py. And run this piece
我的另一个 Python 文件 其为 entertainment_center.py 并运行这个
of code. It will throw an error. The error will happen,
代码 它会抛出一个错误 这个错误会发生
because when we try to create the movie, Toy
因为当我们尝试创建电影 玩具
Story, the init function gets called, which is now
总动员时 init 函数被调用 其现在
looking for several arguments or pieces of information, although,
在寻找多个参数或者信息 尽管
we are not sending it any information whatsoever. So
我们不发送任何的信息 所以
let me change that. Now, I know that first
让我改变一下 现在 我知道第一个
argument for the edit function is, self. Which is
edit 函数的参数是 self 其默认
added by default in Python. So I will skip
被 Python 添加 所以我会跳过
it. The next one is movie title, which I know
它 下一个是电影标题 我知道的是
is, Toy Story, so I will add that. After that, is the movie
玩具总动员 那么我会添加它 之后 是电影
storyline, so I will type that in next. A Story. Of
故事情节 所以我会输入它 一个
a boy and his toys that come to
男孩和他的活过来的玩具的
life. The next one is, the power image, so I will add that.
故事 下一个是 有力的图像 所以我将加上它
[SOUND] I had previously gone on Wikipedia and found a link to, Toy Story's
我已经在维基百科上找到一个 玩具总动员的海报
poster, so I added that and finally, the Youtube trailer, which I will add also.
的链接 所以我加上它最后 Youtube 预告 我也加上了
[SOUND] There it is. Now, let me just scroll
好了 现在 让我滚动回
back so we can see the beginning of the
去使我们可以看到代码的
code. Here, I recognize that you can't see all
开始 这里 我发现你不能看到所有的
of the code, so what I've done is, take an
代码 那么我做的是 用代码的
image of the code, and put it in the
图像 接着将它放在
instructor notes for you to look at. All right,
导师笔记中以便你看 好的
the last thing I'm going to do here, is
我要做的最后一件事是
type Toy Story's story line. Let me save this file,
输入玩具总动员的故事情节 让我保存这个文件
and then go back to my class Movie file, and save that one also. And then
接着回到我的类 Movie 的文件 接着保存它 然后
come back again, to my entertainment_center.py file. Now
再回来 到我的 entertainment_center.py 文件 现在
here, if everything goes correctly, my program should
这里 如果一切顺利的话 我的程序应该
print out, toy_story.storyline. Let's run it. And there
输出 toy_story.storyline 让我们运行它 接着
it is, Toy story, storyline is getting printed.
看 玩具总动员 故事情节输出了
Okay, so, in the next video we are
好的 那么 在下一个视频我们
going to see what happens behind the scenes when
将看看在屏幕后面发生了什么当
we run this piece of code.
我们运行这个代码